techi.com 2013-05-24

# Disclaimer and Privacy Policy | Techi.com

**Privacy Policy Statement  
As a technology news website, Techi (“Techi”, “Website”) is committed to the security of your information and pledges to follow the terms set out in this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).**

**Website Information Usage  
We use web stat services to track the location, browser, operating system and screen resolution of our visitors, but not private information about each individual (such as your name of email address). E-mail addresses are only ever provided by the user voluntarily through the commenting process or via e-mail communications. Note: E-mail addresses that are entered in the required “e-mail” field in the comments area, are not publicly displayed. We aggregate user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by readers, such as survey information and/or Website registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Website in a technical fashion only and not for marketing purposes.**

**Public Information**  
Our Website enables you to post information to be accessed by others through our comments. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data and attempt to contact you off the site. Techi cannot be held liable for any offsite communications that result from your posting of personal information on our site. If you do not wish to be contacted offsite by other Techi visitors, do not give your e-mail address or website address in the content when leaving a comment. Please note: Although you are required to provide your e-mail address in the specified field  when entering a comment, your e-mail address will only be available to the Techi website administrators and will not be publicly visible.

**Advertisers**  
Third-party advertisers featured on Techi may collect tracking information in a different manner than is set out in this Privacy Policy. The only information that they will be able to track is basic Website usage information; e-mail addresses are not passed on to advertisers for any reason even if they are provided to Techi voluntarily.  
****

**Cookies  
We use cookies to store visitor preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, customize Website content based on visitor browser type or other information that the visitor sends.**

**Use of Information Provided By User  
We do not use the information provided by users, such as e-mail addresses and contents of e-mail, for any marketing purposes. Your personal information is not used by subsidiary organizations or businesses related to Techi, unless clearly disclosed for specific situations.**

**Information Ownership**  
All e-mails, comments or other forms of communication received by Techi are the property of Techi and may be used for editorial or technical improvements to the Website at our discretion without any form of compensation being owed to the sender of said communications.

**Information Security  
We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities and the facilities of our service providers to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Website.**

Information provided by Website visitors is held in confidence and used for editorial and technical improvements to the Website.

**Privacy Contact  
If you feel that this Website is not following this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at with your concerns.**
